[Music]
whenever I go all I see is this clock
staring back at me no God in funerals
Mali wouldn't have approved himself head
of the BBC this coats yes you said I'd
be taking over as Scrooge no I'm playing
Scrooge that's why I've got the nose
you're paying that ghost of Christmas
yet to come he doesn't have any light
cast said they'd walk if you played
screw what the whole cast I'm the
leading actor no you're the worst actor
in a company Artie Diana you promised
just hurry up
well you'll have to do it over the phone
then honey honey I cover anywhere lines
it's game it's the nerves come with me
what if you become ill I won't what if
you get injured I would have to be
completely incapacitated to pull out now
good evening BBC viewers unfortunately
the cast of the christmas carol have all
been taken ill the corny polytechnic
drama society happened to be passing by
and will be filling in with special
guest narrator Sandra's aunt Dame Diana
Rigg please enjoy a Christmas carol
[Music]
[Applause]
humming back us confounded times
everywhere I go oh I see is that damn
look everywhere I go all I see is that
damn clock staring back no good in
funerals anyhow ma they wouldn't approve
himself waste of money waste of time
[Music]
Marnie was dead to begin with there is
no doubt whatever
[Music]
the register of his burial was signed by
the solemn Undertaker and of course the
only mourner his partner mr. Scrooge
[Music]
on today on yon go on Christmas Eve
Scrooge walked into his counting-house
he is a tight fisted hand on the
grindstone a squeezing wrenching
grasping scraping covetous old sinner
who was as hard as
the weather was biting but cold and heat
had little influence on Scrooge no
wintry weather could chill him no wind
that blew was bitterer and he
there was not a man woman or child in
London who chose to walk close to
Scrooge in the street but as long as he
was able to go about his business with
Swift and count his coins what it's
Grudge care
Merry Christmas mr. Scrooge Merry
Christmas Uncle God save you humbug
Christmas a humbug uncle you don't mean
that I'm sure I do Francis what's
Christmas but another time if I just
have a year older I'm not an hour richer
every idiot who goes about with Merry
Christmas on his lips should be boiled
with his own pudding and buried with a
stake of Holly through his heart
wipe that stupid smile from your face I
have every reason to smile uncle and
make merry at this time of year what
reason have you to be merry you're poor
enough what reason have you to be dismal
you're rich enough what else can I be
without live in such a world of fools as
this why is what a fool for wishing her
uncle and Merry Christmas because it
does you no good does me no good it is
the one time in the long calendar of the
year where men and women can open their
shutup hearts Britney and hold out their
hands to those below them as their true
Cubs pan yinz
I in speech Francis you belong in
Parliament Christmas uncle though it is
never for a scrap of gold in my pocket
that's pretty good and will do me good
and I say
miss Frances what a pleasure it is to
see you Merry Christmas Bob Cratchit a
merry Christmas to you too
we hear a knock at the door a knock at
the door that must be raising money for
the orphanage what Mary Bowles and
charitable souls they are by the
pleasure of addressing mr. Scrooge or
mr. Marley died seven years ago this
very day oh I'm sorry to hear that
we are raising money for the orphanage
to care for the sick Liam make provision
for the poor like young Jean here on the
show yes mr. Scrooge Merry Christmas
miss Francis
[Music]
capacitated Oh Mario step in
shall I put you down for mr. Scrooge
nothing yeah wish to be anonymous I wish
to be left alone and keep my money what
would you want for the needy
that they should die and decrease the
surplus population I have not much in my
coin purse fear not mr. Cratchit you are
poorer than most but what little I have
you are welcome to I'm afraid there is
only a single penny I have saved you
would part with your only coin yes
do you not need it for your family No
thank you mr. Cratchit you'd give all
you have to charity no no you don't want
to give to charity yes are you sure no
make a choice make a choice will you
give them the coin yes this bag was made
in China god bless you change may the
generosity of the goodly people of
London town keep you merry this
Christmas
Merry Christmas miss Fran says Merry
Christmas mr. Cratchit to you don't be
cross uncle say you'll come and dine
with us tomorrow Christmas alone finally
keep Christmas in your own way
keep it in mind keep it but you don't
keep it me leave it alone very well
uncle if you change your mind you have
our address
Merry Christmas
[Laughter]
you'll want all day tomorrow I suppose
if it's quite convenient sir it's not
convenient
Bob credit Christmas comes but once a
year the cup side of the people going
about their business with glee this is
not a time for money but for family and
mine would appreciate me home sir spare
me a foolish humbug Cratchit aye aye I
am NOT a rich man
if I can spend Christmas with my family
I would be content to know upon the bone
or sleep on a bed of warts
can't you take the whole day
[Music]
bless you thank you but be here all the
earlier the next morning Wang
[Music]
humbucker screws
shaken by the vision went to search the
rooms of his house for signs of the
intruder
finding nothing untoward he returned to
his bedroom secure in the knowledge the
house was completely empty other than
Scrooge
[Music]
okay
Oh
huh Mac
Hunter craves it higher in life I was
your partner Jacob Marley you don't
believe in me why do you doubt your
senses because a little thing affects
them you may be an undigested bit of
beef a blot of mustard his there's more
of gravy than the grave about you the
chain I forged in life I made it link by
link and yard by yard
you let's listen my time isn't a captive
by my deeds but like Christ chain what's
inside so hung heavy around you stay
away by all spinach I wish you see no
more of you
you'll be haunted by three spirits
without their visits you cannot hope to
shun the path I tread expect the first
when the Bell Tolls one farewell screw
Scrooge was left alone again he looked
out through his window which was locked
shut
undisturbed just as it was before the
ghost arrived resolved to forget what he
had experienced Scrooge went to bed and
blew out the light
[Music]
are you the spirit whose coming was
foretold to me who and what are you come
close and I shall tell you I am the
ghost of Christmas past
I shine with the light of a thousand
Christmases gone I have never seen your
like before may I look closer
by my light you shall see the truth of
your past take me in your hand Scrooge
[Music]
your past is hidden beyond these walls
step through with me I am mortal spirit
I cannot by my light you shall
[Applause]
it's--we mr. Scrooge and with that
Scrooge in the spirit disappeared from
his bedroom I would disappear just
screwed found himself soaring and mr.
Scrooge my light shall show you the man
you once were
[Laughter]
welcome to green screen one two three
well it's just one click you can be on a
beach or at the Eiffel Tower overlay
your own exciting footage
I think Robert would make a great
leading actor come on 70s a Scrooge not
even easy huge
I want to meet a grown-up relationship I
don't want to be dating nuts anymore
when you're gonna do it
after we finished Christmas Carol yeah
[Music]
you already haven't I know this place I
grew up here this is where Burrell and I
would caught and there we are
[Music]
I'm sorry ever Nisa we cannot be
together any longer why might love
another Idol has displaced me that you
love more
who is this Idol you speak up there is
no one else the pursuit of wealth and
gain engrosses you I don't understand
you have good hard and unfeeling like a
partner mr. Marley please don't leave me
our contract is an old one made when we
were both poor I can change you are
changed when it was made you were a
different man I release you with a heart
full of love for the man you once were
goodbye my dearest goodbye my dear Oh
spit it why do you delight in torturing
me dry your tears Ebenezer you must to
bed before the other spirits arrive
Oh some nature
and just as Jacob Marley said upon the
stroke of tool
Scrooge had the merry sound of laughter
oh who is bedded I am the ghost of
Christmas present
i'm giad i enjoy a Christmas come know
me better man no spirit I have seen
enough for one night
I cannot bear another heartbreak I beg
you leave me be
hot me no longer
[Applause]
worry not Scrooge your journey with me
shall not be one of heartbreak but at
Merce now come you look hungry
what is all this why it is the bounty of
Christmas feed me tell me it's finished
the purpose of your visit each year you
have shunned the present but this year
you will mark the lessons it holds
conduct me where you will if you have
aught to teach me I shall listen and
profit by it then follow me to the
street Scrooge
tell me something I may smile upon
Jacobi for God's sake
come down to the street Scrooge and see
how the goodly people celebrate
Christmas a day where all the mankind
can forget their position and go about
with glee and good tidings masters and
servants judges and scoundrels landlords
and lodgers could all make merry
together and wish each other well do you
recognize this house Scrooge
hi cheers Bob Cratchit's house for sure
here comes his youngest Tiny Tim walking
home ah Tiny Tim the sweetest dearest
boy that there ever was
[Applause]
oh ho ho
it comes Scrooge look through the window
and observe how these humble folk lives
how about the children clean up before
we eat well we'd be having for Christmas
dinner Bob Bob
[Laughter]
a goose Oh Bobby saved up for it how
wonderful anything for you my sweet a
drop to drink oh why thank you
how was Tiny Tim at church as good as
gold and better he told me coming home
people saw him because he was a cripple
and it might be pleasant for them to
remember upon Christmas Day who made
lame beggars walk and blind men see
enough wine for you my dear plenty high
pray for him every day here he comes now
hello mama
[Laughter]
Tim come here my little boy lift me in
your arms papa we Oh Tim you do look
frail of late free free O'Neill atchoo
failed get out to the table my little
Tim
oh mama
now let us raise a glass to mr. Scrooge
the founder of the feast the founder of
the feast indeed that hard unfeeling
scoundrel is the cause of our suffering
mr. Scrooge has not the kind family I
have known on Christmas Day we may be
poor but we are rich in company Oh
mr. Scrooge may never know
- mr. Scrooge god bless us everyone
a remarkable boy tell me spirit if Tiny
Tim will live I see a vacant seat and a
crutch without an owner I really paid
Bob so poorly they have such a meager
feast what a fine family they are Tiny
Tim was such a brave boy
mrs. Cratchit such a loyal and devoted
woman but they should get on with dying
and decrease the surplus population
should they not but more can you afford
to pay I don't only care about myself do
I come there is more to see do you
recognize this house Scrooge it belongs
to my niece countess there she is now
yeah it looks like they've got the
decorators in sure they'll be done any
moment now
[Laughter]
vegetable vegetable no mineral then not
a mineral which leaves you with quite so
alive
more or less oh my dear Frances why must
you always be so cryptic is this animal
disagreeable or friendly or disagreeable
for sure
does it growl sometimes is it founded
England
it's found in London topper a horse no
but it says nay more than a holster
is it a pig easy to park is this animal
domesticated Francis I know what it is
a disagreeable creature but none of
these it is your uncle Ebenezer Scrooge
a disagreeable creature is that what
they think and the growling one but what
a Scrooge care with these fools believe
I don't care
indeed more or less dead hardly
domesticated or childish blabber I care
perhaps a little the time has come for
me to away and let in another spirit
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you a ghost of Christmas yet to come
[Music]
saundra I've got good news
that agent just called he's going to
take me on
he said the exposure from Christmas
Carol will easily get me that advert
we'll never have to work with this bunch
of freaks again
[Music]
I don't suppose anyone will attend the
old goats funeral
[Music]
he never gave a penny to charity he's
stoic in the poor selfish
[Music]
in it show me some tenderness connected
with a death or this dark conversation
will be forever present to me
[Music]
oh my poor Tim be at peace my dear sweet
boy
[Applause]
[Music]
yes like a week ago I heard good lord I
thought he'd never die well I certainly
shan't miss him all right
he was very unpopular
[Music]
beautiful
are these the shadows of things that
will be or either shadows of things that
may only be
[Music]
Oh spirit a man may change the course of
his life
[Music]
spirit I'm sorry I have been greedy and
selfish I've served myself before others
and shut out the gift of their
kindnesses I'm sorry to everyone all of
you I've taken all for granted I thought
I wanted to go it alone but truth is I'd
be lost without you
in fact I believe
I'm not feeling so well
I think I may be completely
incapacitated Scrooge what
I'm completely incapacitated mr. Scrooge
it's I I don't know what to say I
couldn't you have to they're all
counting on our lead actor Chrissy
it's your part and you should finish it
I'm not gonna take your role well why
don't we do it together
no I'll do it
Scrooge fell before the spirit and
worked to find himself in bed good
morning live in the past present and the
future the spirits of all three shall
strive within me you there child
what day is it Christmas Day I'm Jacob
Marley be praised wait but I must speak
with you Scrooge know Chris is playing
Scrooge plays you took over screws Harry
took over scooch could you force me to
take over his screwed I did not force
you to take a risk route or anything you
forced me to play screwed by being such
a bad actor nobody fault I either of you
two plays Scrooge you came here and took
screwed from me
by for fighting look it doesn't matter
who's playing Scrooge that's what we've
learned tonight it's not that I've
learned tonight I've learned that in
absolutely matters
Kris understudy
[Music]
[Applause]
we're still filming some action here's a
better idea why don't we all go to the
poulterer's
and fetch a goose we shall take it to
Bob Cratchit's house ding dong merrily
the sky
[Music]
everyone we must search for the purpose
juice we can find jingle bells jingle
bells jingle oh who then Bob Cratchit if
this is what you desire most then it is
what you shall have for everyone that
Christmas loves GU Jones sorry would you
mind if we went ahead greetings good
fellow
hi I would like to purchase these fine
GU Jones please it's 399 please anyone
have any much you have any money
No left my coin purse in my other
britches and I have any money left
Elaine
might you be able to open your heart to
those in need at Christmas I'm sorry
please give us Snickers take on yourself
and this lady shopping spree
whatever you say Merry Christmas Bob
Patty's house and present him with the
finest Christmas feast he had in all his
life
[Laughter]
Steve greeting we are travelling the
town to wish everyone a Merry Christmas
oh that's nice
might we enter and spread our joy to the
fine town soaked within not with that
pass oh dear that is a shame
we had hoped we might be able to get
back in the studio but oh and that's the
fire alarm and you could all just make
your way out of the building and it was
the courtyard thank you all of you
well show you in there no I'm here
Minik Christmas Bob and Mary a Christmas
and I have given you in many a year may
I come in I have come here to tell you
but I intend to double your salary and
shall endeavor to assist your struggling
family to assist your struggling family
Tiny Tim shall walk again and I shall
keep Christmas in my heart first then it
has all have a Christmas dinner what do
you say Bob yes
[Music]
attention everyone sorry and sir before
we finished there's something I'd like
to say - max you're gonna break up with
me oh yeah what's wrong with you break
up with you yeah I saw the video you
said you didn't want to be dating
anymore I don't want to be dating
anymore
I want to be married to me yes I I had a
whole plan oh I was gonna propose but
but I saw you kissing Chris
that's my sister
you were going to propose yeah but
that's it Christmas again all of you it
wasn't enough to ruin the production
last year
now you've sabotage mine so go on get
out of here we are going to perform our
version from the top now but it's a
proposal you know I don't care I'm going
to give my performance the only chance
you have of continuing is if I am
completely incapacitated
[Applause]
come on Jerry
and so as Tiny Tim observed please god
bless
[Music]
well that went ah well a Christmas carol
goes wrong DVD and digital download is
available to pre-order now and next on
BBC one
The Avengers re assembled to face their
toughest ever challenge it's time to
chill ahead of tomorrow night's
festivities our Saturday night film is
next
[Music]
you